We design our projects
to be challenging,
我们的项目很有挑战性
and you'll almost certainly
feel frustrated at times.
而且 几乎肯定的是每个学习的人都会感觉到有些困难
But what's unique about learning with
Udacity is that we provide you with
但是 在优达学城学习唯一确定的事实是我们提供
several kinds of human, personal support
options to make sure you succeed and
的职业教练 个性化的支持选项
graduate.
都能确保每位学员顺利毕业
To find out more about this,
I'm going to bring Lisbeth.
更多的信息 由利斯贝为大家介绍
>> I'm Lisbeth Ortega,
Udacity's community manager.
我叫利斯贝奥尔特加 优达学城的社区主管
To begin with,
首先
every project you create is code
reviewed with detailed personal feedback
你所创建的每一个项目都会被我们和蔼的专家编码 评估
by a friendly expert and returned to
you, on average, within 24 hours.
大概在24小时内得到详细 个性化的反馈
You simply can't get personalized
feedback like this anywhere else.
在其他别的地方 你不可能得到像这样的个性化反馈
And, additionally, you can submit these
projects as many times as you need.
另外 你可以根据自己的时间来提交项目
Our reviewers are trained, vetted,
我们的审查员都接受过培训 考核
global experts who love to provide
critical feedback and help you grow.
国际性专家提供关键的反馈 帮助你成长
Additionally, you have access to
a dedicated helpful mentor who
另外 你也可以申请一个专门的导师
acts as a personal adviser
throughout the program.
在整个过程中他将作为你的私人顾问
Your mentor is always accessible, and
you can reach out to them when you need.
你的导师平易近人 可以随时联系他
They'll help you stay on track and make
the most of your Udacity experience.
导师们不仅帮助你们保持正确的学习方向
而且确保你们在优达学城拥有美好的体验
This is another service you'll
only find with us at Udacity.
这也是你们在优达学城唯一能找到的另一项服务
If you have particular technical
questions, you can ask them on our
如果你有特殊的技术问题 可以在我们的论坛咨询他们
forums and receive answers from Udacity
staff so that you'll never stay stuck.
及时的接收到我们员工回复 以保证不会耽误你的学习进程
Finally, our student body is the most
important part of the Udacity
最后 每一个学生个体都是我们优达学城经历中
experience.
最重要的部分
Our students form a worldwide community
of which you are now an integral member.
我们的学生组成了一个世界性的社区
在这个社区里 每个学员都是不可或缺的
In this nanodegree program,
在所有的优达学城项目中
as in all Udacity programs, your peers
will be an invaluable resource to you.
像这样的纳米学位项目 你的伙伴将会是你的无价之宝
And just as in a brick and
就像砖头跟砂浆机一样
mortar institution,
it's important to get to know them.
彼此了解才是最重要的
To facilitate this, we work hard
to introduce you to your peers.
为了解决这个问题 我们会努力促进你们彼此认识
In particular,
we'll arrange both online and
为此 我们特安排了线上线下学习组
offline study groups where
you'll meet face to face.
在这些学习组里 成员们可以面对面交流
We'll support students meetups and
industry events,
我们支持学生参加聚会和关注行业动态
and engender a community atmosphere
to ensure your learning experience is
旨在创造出一种能够让你们的学习生涯更加充实的
as rich as possible.
社区氛围
We'll also help you interact online
through our forums, Slack and
我们也很鼓励大家通过我们的论坛 Slack
other online tools.
还有其他的在线工具进行线上互动
>> Thank you, Lisbeth.
谢谢你 利斯贝
Here at Udacity we've built a fantastic
support network to help students
我们在优达学城建立了一个非常棒的支持网络来帮助学生
like you surpass your expectations.
爱你如期而至
We hope you take full advantage of these
resources to reach your goals and more.
我们希望你们能充分利用这些资源来达到你的目标
并且收获更多